let quizz = [
    {
    question: " The Amazon Reef is located in which ocean ?",
    option: [
        "Pacific Ocean",
        "Atlantic Ocean",
        "Indian Ocean",
        "Artic Ocean",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "Which is the first planet to have been discovered by the use of telescope ?",
    option: [
        "Jupiter",
        "Mars",
        "Uranus",
        "Saturn",
    ],
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "Who gave theory of Relativity ?",
    option: [
        "Isaac Newton",
        "Albert Einstein",
        "Galileo Galilei",
        "Archimedas",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "Who was the interim president of first Constituent assembly ?",
    option: [
        "Dr.Rajendra Prasad",
        "Sachidanand Sinha",
        "BR Abmedkar",
        "Jawharlal Nehru",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "When was the Olympic Council of Asis formed ?",
    option: [
        "1990",
        "1981",
        "1989",
        "1982",
    ],
    answer: 4,
},
{
    question: " Which of the followinf ancient Tamil kingdoms came to be known from Sangam Literature",
    option: [
        "Chola",
        "Chera",
        "Pandya",
        "All of these Above",
    ],
    answer: 4,
},
{
    question: "Where was the first Tamil Sangam held ?",
    option: [
        "Madurai",
        "Kapadapuram",
        "Kaverpattinam",
        "Kural",
    ],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: " Capital of Chola Dynasty ?",
    option: [
        "Madurai",
        "karur",
        "Kaverpattinam",
        "Uraiyur",
    ],
    answer: 4,
},
{
    question: " Turmeric Belongs to from which one of the following family of plants",
    option: [
        "Radish",
        "Onion",
        "Clove",
        "Ginger",
    ],
    answer: 4,
},
{
    question: "Which of the following is the simpliest amino acid ?",
    option: [
        "Glycine",
        "Tyrocine",
        "Alanine",
        "Asparagine",
    ],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: "Which Microsoft-based technology was built to link desktop apps to world wide web ?",
    option: [
        "Active Channel",
        "Active Desktop",
        "Active X",
        "None of these Above",
    ],
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "How many phases does a compiler has ?",
    option: [
        "3",
        "5",
        "7",
        "8",
    ],
    answer: 4,
},
{
    question: "International MotherLanguage Day ?",
    option: [
        "mar 6",
        "feb 21",
        "oct 18",
        "Jan 10",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "What is the S.I unit of Activity ?",
    option: [
        "Becquerel",
        "curie",
        "candela",
        "henry",
    ],
    answer: 3,
}
]